♪ I like it like that ♪
♪ You gotta believe
me when I tell you ♪
♪ I said I like it like that ♪
♪ You gotta believe
me when I tell you ♪
♪ I said I like it… ♪
♪ Now I like dollars,
I like diamonds ♪
♪ I like stunting,
I like shining ♪
♪ I like million dollar deals ♪
♪ Where's my pen?
Bitch, I'm signin'… ♪
- Maybe we should've forfeited.
- Come on now. It's just a bit of rain.
Yo, Coach Harris, do you
think we could pull over?
I gotta take a piss.
No way. You should've
done that before we left.
Come on, man. I did!
- Yeah? What was that for?
- Practice.
Practice makes
perfect. Ain't that right, V?
Bro, according to your
average on penalty kicks,
you should work on your
aim every chance you get.
- Oh shit!
- Chip!
Vero!
As Hurricane Abby
gains strength off the coast,
Miami will be seeing strong
wind and rain advisories today.
So stay tuned and stay inside.
- Where is he, Luis?
- Don't you have surgery?
- Come on!
- He's in his office.
- What happened?
- He doesn't want any visitors.
- You talking about Phillips?
- Why are you so wet?
- Biked. Same as always.
- You're a grown man.
I am. And smart enough to know
that leased Beamer's a money pit.
The pit has a soft-top. I'm dry.
What,
are you moving in?
There's a hurricane. It's
called being prepared.
- Danny, you have to get up.
- I am.
- You're lying down.
- And I am preparing to get up.
Come on.
Don't make the day worse
by being late to shift.
- So they know?
- Uh, not the details.
Was
he…? After the…?
- Yeah.
- Was he what? After the what?
Will someone tell me what
the hell is going on?
Yesterday, Phillips got
reported for sexual harassment.
What?
Then he crawled into a fifth of
tequila. Or maybe it was two.
He was in bad shape.
I've never seen him like this.
Did something happen
at the, uh, retreat?
I don't know, man. It's not like
they put that shit in a memo.
This is bullshit. The guy's a saint.
The junior residents love him.
He's the best chief resident we ever
had. This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, does Danny
know about this?
Wait, who reported him?
They knew it was me?
Hey, come on. Sit down.
Come on.
- What's the storm doing?
- Getting bigger.
- Coming towards us?
- Yeah, looks like it.
Great.
Hey.
Remember when we were kids? You
used to sneak us into concerts.
What would you say
about the mosh pit?
Whatever you do,
don't fall down.
Yep. So get your ass
up and go to work.
♪ …we just turn and
look away when… ♪
Oh shit, there she is.
♪ I don't understand how ♪
♪ 'Stand how ♪
♪ The whole world feels
Like a ticking time bomb ♪
You don't think it's weird Danny
didn't tell you? You're like best friends.
It's her story to tell.
And I support her.
'Cause if Phillips gets fired, you're
next in line for chief resident.
Anyone's gonna get fired,
I'd love for it to be you.
Chan. What do you think about
this whole Phillips thing?
I was on all night. I don't got the
energy to represent all women today.
Oh… And what about our
lovely new student here?
Oh. Camila Perez. Third
year med student, UM.
Don't bother. Cole can
hardly remember my name,
and I've worked with him for
two years. Unfortunately.
Good morning, Harriet. Hermione?
Harper Simms.
Second-year EM resident.
Bus crash on their way in.
Mm. Where's your sister?
What? Don't want her to sneak up
while you're talking shit about her?
Too late.
What? You think I'm gonna read a
prepared statement or something?
Three minutes out!
Um…
You okay?
Fantastic.
Why? Something happen?
- That's not funny.
- Cole, back off.
We gonna pretend
everything's normal?
- No one's doing that.
- Danny is doing that.
- Cole.
- Look, I told HR the truth.
It's over. Whether anyone
here supports me or not.
It's a bit hard to support you
when we have no idea what happened.
Is that why it's hard?
Well, I think it was brave.
Thanks.
Whoever you are.
Okay. Everyone, listen up.
I'm gonna make this quick
because we have a bus of patients
that need our full attention.
Chief Resident Phillips has been suspended
pending an internal investigation.
This means we'll need to appoint
a replacement on an interim basis.
You got your speech ready?
And with the full
support of the faculty…
I have chosen Danny Simms.
Shit.
Whoo.
So let's give her the same
respect we always afforded Dr. Phillips,
and let's get through
this day. Okay?
I would like you to meet your new
Chief Resident, Dr. Xander Phillips.
- Just transferred in from Kennedy.
- Hey guys, nice to meet you.
Kennedy, huh? Why transfer?
Better fleeces, obviously.
You like this, don't you? Yeah. Okay.
No, look, I do know this is
unusual, so I will be honest.
Kennedy's been good to me, but McGuire
was my first choice for residency.
Probably for the same reason
as it was for all of you guys.
'Cause Dr. Cruz.
She built this place into the best
Level I Trauma Center in the state.
Thank you. But you've
already got the job.
It's them you need to convince now.
That's
easy, Dr. Cruz.
What do you think about the
pastelitos at Versailles?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Take your time.
I've had better.
We're
gonna get along.
Dr. Cruz.
- Dr. Cruz, you can't.
- Can't what?
- You can't promote me. Not now.
- Why not?
Because it doesn't look good.
Well, this
is where we are.
You didn't want it
to be me, did you?
I'm sure you'll prove
to us why it should be.
Less than a minute!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
- What have you got?
- Cyclist on the causeway.
Got caught in a multiple car
crash. We lost pulses en route.
- Where's surgery?
- I got it.
Uh, trauma one.
If he gets pulses
back and needs the OR,
turf him quick
'cause I need you.
Seventeen-year-old male with obvious
head trauma, blown left pupil.
- Harper.
- I got him.
Gabe, call neurosurgery. Let me
get ahead to set up for an airway.
Chip Harris, bus
driver and team coach.
Got a chest full of windshield and
water. Hypotensive. GCS of ten.
He's critical. Get
him to trauma two.
I got it. Stay on triage.
Oh, Dr. Simms, right?
You know this guy?
Santino Cuesta,
he was my patient.
Came in with a dog bite
yesterday. He was fine.
He's not anymore. Family
found him unconscious.
His pressure's tanking.
- Give me an 8.0 ET tube, please.
- The bite was superficial.
We cleaned it, updated his
tetanus, gave him antibiotics…
All right, suction, please.
I can see the cords.
He was still tachy on discharge.
It's not the bite. It's the dog.
He needs a FAST exam. I bet
he's got a ruptured spleen.
It's in. Bag him. I need a
portable chest X-ray and an EKG.
- Did you say ruptured spleen?
- His abdomen's distended.
The dog, they have this huge bullmastiff.
He said it knocked him down a few times.
It must have been the impact,
not the bite. I…
I missed it.
It's possible, but
that is a big leap.
- It'll kill him if you don't move fast.
- Hey. Take a breath.
You just got here and you wanna
tell me what to do with my patient?
You take a breath, dude.
Sorry.
Name
four kinds of nuts.
- What?
- Four kinds of nuts or get out.
Um…
Pistachio,
walnut, almond, peanut.
- Peanut is a legume, but close enough.
- Give me the ultrasound.
You think I'm right?
Let's find out. Now that you've picked
yourself out of the ceiling fan,
I have a feeling you might
be a pretty good doctor.
- What've we got?
- 17-year-old male from the crash.
- Stable vitals with an amputated hand.
- Trauma one. This way.
Monitoring,
140, it's good.
Ready? One, two, three.
- Okay. Where's the hand?
- Rescuers are still searching.
You're new.
- Started a few weeks ago.
- Wasn't a question.
This dressing looks like
it was done at Chipotle.
- Excuse me?
- What's your name, kid?
Okay, loud and clear.
Let's get him a 75 fentanyl for the
pain and call ortho and vascular.
I do want to know
your name, though.
Okay? And here's
why. Look at me.
I need to know your name
because I'm responsible for you.
I'm going to bother people about
you. I'm going to worry about you.
I want to know who I'm worrying
about. Okay, how about this?
You just nod when
I get to it, right?
You look like you
could be a Josh.
Kevin…
Marie?
Tyler.
Tyler Marie. Beautiful.
Okay.
- My hand.
- Hey. Hey.
- My hand, man.
- Hey. They're looking for it.
And I'm not gonna let them
stop. I promise. Okay.
- What are you waiting for, Chan?
- Uh, yeah. What do you need?
What do I need? You don't
wait for me to tell you.
You tell me what I need. Right?
I can help stabilize the
arm so you can unwrap him?
There we go. The new girl came
to work today. Get in here.
Chan, you can go back to sleep.
Vero. Is she here?
Vero?
Ugh… My friend. Vero. She was
sitting next to me. Is she here?
I don't know, mate. We can find
out, but what was her last name?
Vero Cruz. Vero Cruz.
We've got to find her.
The water was so black.
Uh, did you say Vero Cruz?
Okay, tell Danny.
Hey, hey, hey.
Tyler, I'm on it, okay?
We'll find her, okay?
Good morning,
Natalie. How are you?
Good, and how are you, Ruben?
You know, hanging out.
Is that the cyclist
from the bridge?
Yes.
Ruben.
Just say it.
Okay, look…
A hurricane is coming.
Right now it's raining.
And when it makes landfall?
We'll lock it down and ride it out.
That's what this place was built for.
Days like this, I bet you wish
the ER wasn't run by
the surgery department.
It's hard to let go of something
I built from nothing, but…
That is not
what you're getting at.
Okay. All right.
Listen, on the harassment thing,
I have no opinion, all right?
Nor is it your concern.
Fine. But maybe not the best day to
have a sudden change in leadership.
Natalie, please.
Phillips,
he's a rock down there.
He was the one
everyone looked to.
Danny Simms is a capable doctor.
She's so capable,
she can lead a short-staffed ER
in the city's only Level I Trauma Center,
and all of that through a hurricane?
I am trying to avoid a legal and PR
shitstorm that we will be hit with
if we are not mindful about our
response to a complaint like hers.
Especially one involving
Xander Phillips.
It's a lot of
confidence you're putting in Simms.
Yes, it is.
And I hope you have the
same confidence in me.
I'm Dr. Simms. I
hear you need some stitches.
Yeah, that's me.
They just numbed it, actually.
Y'all are lucky.
Dr. Simms gives some
world-class stitches.
All right, my man. I
think you're gonna live.
Let's see about that
glass. Shall we?
- Am I gonna have a scar?
- Do you want a scar?
I mean, girls like scars, right?
I like guys who read books.
- Hey, you doing okay?
- Me?
- Why?
- Oh, come on.
It can't feel good to lose
out on that promotion.
Nah, she's my friend.
I'm happy for her.
Well, that's big of you.
Before Phillips, she wasn't
gonna put her name in for chief.
- Didn't think she'd get it.
- Hm.
I always thought she
had a… a real shot.
Just couldn't make her believe
in herself. But I guess he could.
She was always his favorite.
- Hm.
- Everybody knew it.
I just wish I'd known what
she was going through.
Yeah, me too.
Looks really pale.
Persistently hypotensive
despite fluids and blood.
That explains it. He's got a
lot of blood in his abdomen.
I see it.
He's got a positive FAST.
- What's the situation with the ORs?
- Flooded with traumas.
Telling me at least 20 minutes
until they can take him.
Let's transfuse two units of blood
and set up for a central line.
You got it.
He was driving the bus? It's a
hell of a thing to wake up to.
I'm sorry.
I, uh…
I wanted to tell you.
No, that's okay.
You don't have to talk about it.
And you definitely
don't have to apologize.
What about for getting
the job you wanted?
What about that?
Yeah, that I can never forgive.
Come on. It'll be great.
It's not permanent yet.
There's still plenty of
time for me to mess it up.
Danny, it's Cruz. We think her
daughter Vero was on that bus.
- Is she in the ER?
- Not yet, but more are coming in.
- Where's Cruz?
- Scrubbed in on the cyclist.
- Okay, send someone up to tell her.
- No.
- No?
- No, I don't think we should.
The chair's daughter might've been
on that bus and you don't think...
And she's in surgery.
We'd be distracting her with a
hypothetical while she's operating.
- Danny, I really think...
- I know what you think.
Look, if Vero comes in,
we will tell her then.
Okay?
Yeah. Your call.
Hurricane
Abby is making landfall.
So those in the city are
encouraged to shelter in place.
However, those residents
along the coastline
need to evacuate immediately and
get to a shelter in the city…
First big hurricane?
First one that seems
to be aiming at me.
Growing up here, I've been
through a bunch of these.
Usually it's just the anticipation
that's the worst part.
Indiana, it was tornadoes.
Get the warnings all the time.
It's when the sky turns green,
then you start worrying.
Well, should we start worrying?
Oh, um…
I don't know. It's hard to say.
But I guess it doesn't look like
we're leaving anytime soon, right?
So…
Well, I hope you brought your
stuff. Looks like a lot of upkeep.
What do you mean?
Look, it's not that
you don't look great.
It's just the…
style around here
is sort of a…
malnourished exhaustion.
So you're saying I stand out?
Kinda.
Yeah.
Well, good.
I plan to.
Need a doctor over here!
- Yeah.
- Adult male.
Blunt force trauma to chest,
increased work of breathing.
Trauma bays are
full. Go to room two.
- Uh, Sophie, where's Cole?
- Cole's in with the amputation.
All right. Come
on. You're with me.
BP is 60 and
falling. Pulse ox 75.
- What do his lungs sound like?
- No breath sounds on the left.
- Pulse ox is falling. He's crashing.
- I need to intubate.
I'll deal with his chest
in a minute. Here you go.
- Clear. Suction.
- I got it.
Great.
What is she doing?
- He needs a chest tube.
- And you're doing it? Elijah!
- Hold on. It can wait.
- It can't, and I can do it.
Okay.
Okay, she's doing it.
Guys, we've lost pulses.
Sophie, you need to move faster.
- What's going on?
- I've got it. I'm fine.
We still don't have pulses.
We should start compressions.
- Let me do it.
- You told me to jump in. I got it.
I got it.
She did. Nice save.
Pulses are faint,
but they're back.
- What do we got?
- Tension pneumo.
I decompressed the chest
while Dr. Elijah intubated.
Vitals are stabilizing.
Well, he's not dead, so there's
that. But that chest tube is low.
Let's just pray you didn't
lacerate his spleen.
Tom, did you supervise this?
No, I just got here.
- Don't know what she was thinking.
- Come on, you told me to jump in.
Tom, just supervise her,
okay? Better, all right?
And call me when the CT's back.
- Cass? Uh…
- Yeah, I got you.
What?
I mean… you could have been a
little more supportive of Sophie.
Phillips was supportive of
Danny. Look where that got him.
I don't think that was the main issue.
Hey, look, um, I just wanted
to say what happened earlier…
Danny getting your job. You
didn't make a scene. That was…
Well…
you're a better man than me.
Let's pack him
up. Get him to CT.
Let's give a gram of TXA and
another two units of blood.
But we're running out of time.
Only thing that'll stop
the bleeding is the OR.
Hey. You're still
working on this guy?
We're still not ready.
Well, so put a junior
resident on him until then.
- He's my patient.
- You're hiding.
- I'm not…
- Luis?
…hiding.
- How long has she been in here for?
- No. I don't get involved.
You're chief resident
now. You did hear that, right?
You should be out running the floor,
coordinating traumas, helping residents...
Harper. I know.
I know you know.
And I know that you can do it.
There's a lot of people out there
that need you to start believing that.
You're ready.
I'm not… I'm not ready.
Only because you refuse to be.
It's a festival of gore. How about
I split you open like a turkey,
and you tell me what a
beautiful experience it is?
Know what? I'm gonna say something
you may not have thought of,
and that is that your crippling
fear of pregnant women
might be holding you back
as a medical professional.
- That's ridiculous.
- I've been here nearly a year.
- I've never seen you look one in the eye.
- I'm not afraid of pregnant people.
You're gonna make me
do this, aren't you?
Don't worry. I'll be
right there with you.
Just breathe.
I hate you.
No, you don't.
- Finally. OR's ready.
- BP's coming up.
Danny.
Yeah, okay. Let's
get him moving.
Anchor.
My boys.
Mr. Harris, you were in an accident.
We're gonna take you to surgery.
Is everyone alive?
Huh?
- Did I kill any of my kids?
- We don't know, Mr. Harris.
We are doing everything we can
to get everyone healthy again,
but right now, we need
to get you to the OR.
No, no. No, I'm not going.
You are bleeding internally.
You'll die without surgery.
No, no, no! No, no.
Look, I'm competent,
okay? I know my rights.
I'm not going anywhere until
I know all my kids are okay.
Okay?
Okay.
Oh, hey. You.
Have they heard anything
about that kid Tyler's hand?
- Not yet, no.
- They better be looking.
You let me know.
Will do, Cinnabon.
What?
Oh yeah, that's
what they call you.
Are you not the hothead surgeon that
thinks unfiltered is a personality?
Has a TikTok called "Surgeon
Bruv"? Ghosts women on Hinge?
- TikTok was a one-time thing.
- Yeah, well, paramedics talk.
Turns out I made more friends in my
first week than you have in years.
Hey, why do they
call me Cinnabon?
Take a seat.
We will be right with you.
Hey, Doc. Um, we
were just wondering,
is there any update
on Coach Harris?
Can we see him?
He's on some pretty heavy sedatives,
but I will keep you updated.
- I promise.
- Can you just tell us what's going on?
You're gonna die without that
surgery. Know that, right?
Was it my fault?
The crash.
The boys don't blame you.
They want to know you'll be
okay. They want to see you.
No, I don't want
them coming in here.
I don't want them knowing
I'm refusing treatment.
Don't worry.
Without your consent, no one can
interfere with your quiet, stubborn death.
The… The doctor
in the wheelchair,
did you know she's
my younger sister?
No.
Really?
When we were kids, we
used to… fight, hard.
I mean… throwing each other
over tables, ripping out hair.
One day, um… she
was up in my room,
and… and she said something
that I didn't like, and…
And I saw the stairs.
"That would be new," I thought.
So I pushed her.
I, um…
I had all of this adrenaline…
and I pushed her so hard that…
that she didn't
even hit the stairs.
Just the ground.
And now she lives in a chair.
You want to suffer more than
the people you hurt because
if you do, maybe
they'll forgive you.
How do you suffer?
Oh…
I make bad decisions.
I… say shit I shouldn't say.
How's… How's that
working out for you?
Oh, it works great.
Can't do it if
you're dead, though.
Danny!
Dispatch has one more critical
coming in. A minute out.
I heard it could be Vero?
- Do you know what she looks like?
- Yeah.
I can use you, then. Come on.
17-year-old female, blunt
force trauma to the chest.
- BP's crashing, 60 over 40.
- That's her. That's Cruz's daughter.
Trauma one is open.
Okay, people, let's help
her. What do we got?
Abdomen's soft.
- Lungs are clear. Not protecting airway.
- Pulse thready at 150.
- Intubate her. I'll start her FAST.
- I'll start an IV.
You. Go up to the OR and tell Cruz
her daughter's in the trauma bay.
Prepping intubation.
Dr. Cole to…
- Dr. Cole?
- We got all the hands we need, thank you.
Sure you couldn't use one more?
- Looks like a clean cut.
- Danny?
- Go. Kid needs you.
- I'm in. Bag her, please.
- BP's crashing.
- Oh shit. Fluid around the heart.
Pericardial tamponade. She
needs a pericardiocentesis.
- Luis, call cardiac surgery.
- On it.
Push-dose pressors?
We gotta remove the blood
pressing on her heart.
Come on, girlfriend.
Let's get you better.
BP's still
falling. 40 palp.
All right.
Come on. Come on.
Don't go too deep. You don't
want to puncture the heart.
Come on.
I got it.
You got it. BP's coming up.
- Where's cardiac surgery?
- Moving at their regular pace, obviously.
- My God, did anyone tell them who this is?
- I'll run up there now.
Good thing we bought
some time, huh?
- Oh, Dr. Elijah? Hi.
- Hey.
So Dr. Simms told me to tell
Dr. Cruz that her daughter is here,
but I don't know
which OR she's in.
Vero? Vero's here
now? In the ER?
Yeah, she's in the trauma room.
All right.
- Don't worry, I got it. I'll tell her.
- Okay.
Ready to go.
Are you out of your mind? I'm about
to pop this woman's spleen out.
I'm sorry, but I
had to. It's your daughter.
- She's here.
- Here?
She's
downstairs in the ER.
She was on that
bus that crashed.
- I'm just hearing about this now?
- She just got in.
Someone had to
have known she was coming.
Did anyone know
she was coming in?
- Answer my question. Did anybody know?
- Danny told us not to tell you.
Call Dr. Harvey. He
needs to replace me.
Hurry.
Systolic's in the 70s.
- Jesus, where the hell is cardiac surgery?
- Vitals are unstable.
- Blood's reaccumulating around the heart.
- Slowly. The vitals are okay.
I think we just wait for
surgery. Keep pushing pressors…
No, we can't wait.
She needs a drain.
Danny, no. No, no, no. Surgery
should be here any minute.
- Prep for pericardial drain.
- You got it.
If you go one millimeter too far and
you puncture her heart, she dies.
A drain's risky? Wait until she
crashes and we have to crack her chest.
True, but...
But this is the
chair's daughter.
And you're all scared.
But you know what? I
don't give a shit anymore.
It's the right thing to
do, so I am doing it.
Open the kit.
Almost there.
What the hell?
Lost power!
Backup?
- Cardiac surgery's on their way.
- Backup should be on any second.
Ultrasound's out of battery.
They never charge these things.
I have to keep going.
Wait. With no ultrasound,
she'll be totally blind.
Gabe. She can do it.
It's the rain. Substation
downtown was flooded.
Still doesn't explain why our
backup generators haven't kicked on.
Something's wrong.
I've
got a bad feeling.
- What's going on? Stop.
- I can't stop now.
Goddamn it, I'll do it.
I got it.
Putting a catheter
over the wire.
It's in position.
- Or it's in the heart.
- Only one way to find out.
About time.
Come on, come on, come on.
Drainage isn't pulsatile.
- BP?
- It's coming up.
Vitals are improving.
Good job.
Let's get her upstairs
to the OR. Come on.
Dr. Cruz, I...
When did you know my
daughter was coming in?
When?
Um… I knew it was a possibility,
but I wasn't sure until she arrived.
Elijah seemed to be sure.
Who else knew?
I told them not to tell you.
You were in surgery. It
wasn't fair to your patient
to upset you with a
hypothetical. It was my call.
- Bullshit, it was your call.
- Vero wasn't here.
- We didn't have confirmation...
- She's my daughter.
How dare you?
There were a dozen people
you could've consulted
before taking her life
into your own hands.
You were careless. You were
reckless. You were arrogant.
And all you've proved is you have no
understanding of the job I gave you.
Yeah, I didn't know it was my job
to know where your daughter was.
Sorry.
- Danny.
- Thank you so much for your support.
♪ Riding high ♪
♪ When I was your star ♪
♪ Mm-mmm ♪
♪ Lightning strikes ♪
♪ Right at the heart ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ Paradise calling ♪
♪ All I've ever wanted… ♪
How are you feeling?
About… the same as you look.
Bad day?
Me? No.
No.
Just want to make sure
you didn't die alone.
♪ Light us up ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ Oh-ohh ♪
Hey.
♪ This could be the
way out the dark ♪
♪ This could be the spark… ♪
Hey.
Tyler Marie.
♪ This could be the start ♪
♪ Paradise calling… ♪
What did I tell you?
You found my hand?
Yeah, we did.
Well, actually, she found it.
She was very motivated.
She has quite an
obsessive crush on me, so…
Please.
She even gave me a nickname.
It's not flattering.
Thank you.
Yep.
♪ You don't know the
ways of the heart ♪
♪ This could be the start ♪
♪ Both eyes wide open ♪
♪ So high I'm still falling ♪
♪ If you could only feel ♪
♪ Our love ♪
Hey, Coach.
Let us in. We're all
out here for you.
We want you to get to surgery.
We need you to get better.
Oh
God. Why did you…
Told you I say shit
I shouldn't say.
Coach, Coach, Coach!
- We love you, Coach!
Come on, Coach.
Are you gonna say no to them?
No… I'm ready.
♪ Both eyes wide open… ♪
- There he is.
- Come on, Coach.
- Let's go, Coach.
- There he is!
Go get 'em!
Coach!
Stay strong, Coach.
Why do you doubt yourself?
You did a great job
delivering that baby.
- She hated me.
- No, she didn't.
She bit me.
Only because you were in range.
You're avoiding my question.
- I don't doubt myself.
- You assume the worst will happen.
It usually does.
- You know what I think?
- What?
I think you are so afraid
of your own potential,
you self-sabotage.
Mm.
Am I gonna be charged
for this?
Yes.
What are you doing?
- Danny, I…
- No.
I tried calling you.
A few times.
I saw.
- We could've just talked.
- I didn't want to talk.
All right. So you blew
up our lives instead?
You dropped a nuke on
me to prove a point?
This… is why I
didn't want to talk.
If you had just trusted me, none
of this would have happened.
Yeah, it happened
because I did trust you.
- I meant everything I ever said to you.
- No.
You told me what I wanted to hear,
and I was dumb enough to believe it.
Says the person who just lied to a
patient to get him to go to surgery.
Uh-huh, I heard what
you said to that coach.
You didn't push Harper down
the stairs. Your dad did.
I saved his life.
Yeah, and you still lied.
I know what happened
at your old hospital.
I found out the real reason you
got transferred from Kennedy.
That's why you're doing this?
- What is it you think you know?
- Dr. Phillips, Dr. Simms.
This storm, it's
gonna be a direct hit.
And we're gonna ride it out…
but we are understaffed.
This is not a referendum
on your competence,
or your ability to
be a good chief.
And the hospital is taking
your claim extremely seriously.
But we are about to
be in a world of shit.
I think it would be to everyone's
benefit that Dr. Phillips stays to help.
Do you agree, Dr. Simms?
Hm.
Good.
I need you both out there. Now.
Mm. I thought you
didn't want me.
♪ For a while there,
it was rough ♪
♪ But lately, I've
been doin' better ♪
♪ Than the last four
cold Decembers I recall ♪
♪ And I see my
family every month ♪
♪ I found a girl
my parents love ♪
♪ She'll come and stay the night
And I think I might have it all ♪
Hi.
Look, I… I know you're
upset about today.
We said nothing
in public. I just…
I slipped.
♪ And I hold you every night ♪
♪ And that's a feeling
I wanna get used to ♪
♪ But there's no
man as terrified ♪
♪ As the man who
stands to lose you ♪
♪ Oh, I hope I don't lose you ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Please ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ I want you, I
need you, oh God ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Take ♪
♪ These beautiful
things that I've got ♪
♪ Please ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ I want you, I
need you, oh God ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Take ♪
♪ These beautiful
things that I've got ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪